              Central Depository Bangladesh Limited (CDBL)
       Depository Account (BO Account) opened with CDBL Participant
                 Terms & Conditions -Bye Laws 7.3.3(c)
            TREC Holder of Chittagong Stock Exchange Limited TREC Holder No. 056

Dear Sir,
Please open a Depository account (BO Account) in my/our names (s) on the terms and conditions set out bellow. In Consideration of
Kabir Securities Limited (the "CDBL Participant") opening the account providing depository account facilities to me/us. I / we have
signed the BO Account opening Form as a token acceptance of the terms and conditions set out bellow.

1. I/we agree to be bound by the Depositories Act. 1999, Depositories Regulations, 2000, The Depository (User) Regulations 2003,
 and abide by the Bye laws and Operating Instructions issued from time to time by CDBL.
2. CDBL shall allocate a unique identification number to me/us (Account Holder BO ID) for the CDBL Participant to maintain a
 separate Account for me/us, unless I/we instruct the CDBL Participant to keep the securities in an Omnibus Account of the
 CDBL Participant. The CDBL Participant shall however ensure that my / our securities shall not be mixed with the CDBL
 Participant's own Securities.
3. I/we agree to pay such fees, charges and diposits to the CDBL Participant as may be mutually agree upon, for the purpose of
 opening and maintaining my/our account for carrying out the instructions and for rendering such other services as are incidental
 or consequential to my/our holding securities in and in and transactin through the said depository account with the CDBL
 Participant.
4. I/We shall be responsible for :
 (a) The veracity of all statements and particulars set out in the account opening form supporting or accompanying
   documents.
 (b) The authenticity and genuiness of all certificates and/or documents submitted to CDBL Participant along with or in
   support of the account opening form or subsequently for dematerialization.
 (c) Title to the securities submitted to the CDBL Participant from time for dematerialization.
 (d) Ensuring at all times that the securities to the credit of my / our account are sufficient to meet the instructions issued to
   the CDBL Participant for effecting any transaction / transfer.
 (e) Informing the CDBL Participant at the earliest of any changes in my/our account particulars such as address, Bank details,
   status, authorizations, mandates, nomination signature etc.
 (f) Furnishing accurate identification details whilst subscribing to any issue of securities.
5. I / we shall notify the CDBL Participant of any change in the particulars set out in the application form submitted to the CDBL
 Participant at the time of opening the account or furnished to the CDBL Participant from time to time at the earliest. The CDBL
 Participant shall not be liable or responsible for any loss that may be caused to me/us by reason of my/our failure to intimate
 such change to the CDBL Participant at the earliest.
6. Where I / we have executed a BO Account Nomination Form :
 (a) In the event of my / our death, the nominee shall receive / draw the securities held in my / our account.
 (b) In the event, the nominee so authorized remains a minor at the time of my / our death, the legal guardian is authorized to
   receive 7 draw the securities hold in my I our account.
 (c) The nominee so authorized shall be entitled to all my / our account to the exclusion of all other persons i.e my / our heirs,
   executors and administrators and all other persons claiming through or under me / us and delivery of securities to the
   nominee in pursuance of this authority shall be binding on all other persons.
7. I / we may at any time call upon the CDBL Participant to close my / our account with the CDBL Participant provided no instructions
 remain pending or unexecuted and no fees or charges remain payable by me / us to the CDBL Participant. In such event 1 1 we may
 close my/our account by executing the Account Closing form if no balances are standing to my/our credit in the account.
 In case any balances of securities exist in the account my be closed by me / us in one of the following way :
 (a) By dematerialization of all existing balances in my/our account.

