   Forged Shares : Kabir Securities Limited shall not be liable or responsible for any shares that are found to be forged. However,
   Kabir Securities Limited will make every attempt to replace the forged shares from the seller.
   Law : The terms and conditions contained herein shall be governed by and be construed in accordance with the laws of Bangladesh.
   Notices :
          (a) All notices, instructions or other communications shall be given in English and in writing (facsimile, telex, telegram, cable
             or letter) or orally and shall be sent to Kabir Securities Limited and the account holder at the address, fax and / or telex
             number shown herein or at such other address as may be communicated by the parties here to in writing.
          (b) Proof of delivery or dispatch shall be:
             (i) in the case of a letter: dispatch of the letter duly stamped and addressed
             (ii) in the case of facsimile, telex, telegram, or cable on the day of dispatch with physical or actual confirmation.
          (c) All verbal notices, instructions, or other communications should be confirmed in writing within 24 hours.
   Definitions : Words defined herein, save where a contrary meaning appears or such meaning is inconsistent with the context,
   shall have this same defined meaning wherever used.
   Sums Due : For all purposes, including any legal proceedings, a certificate by any of Kabir Securities Limited officers confirming the
   monies and/or liabilities for the time being due and /or incurred to by the account holder shall be conclusive evidence thereof against
   him / her.
   Brokerage Charge : Client shall be bound to pay     % (In word                        ) charges as brokerage
   to broker for buy and sell and broker can change time to time.
   Client shall be bound to furnish such other particulars, documents and/or information that may reasonably require from time
   to time.
   Broker shall have the right to change / modify any terms / conditions when may deem necesssary without any notice to
   the client.
   Disputes and Resolution of Dispute : In case of any dispute arising between the Kabir Securities Limited and the account holder
   in connection with the interpretation or enforcement of the terms and conditions contained herein, attempts should be made to settle
   the matter amicably, in case of failure to settle the matter amicably, the same shall be referred to arbitration of two arbitrators,
   each to be nominated by the parties who shall also appoint an Umpire. The decision of the arbitrators, so nominated, shall be
   binding on both the parties. The arbitration shall be conducted in accordance with the Arbitration Act, 2001.
   I / We have read the terms and conditions contained herein above, and having agreed with such terms and conditions I / we put
   my / our / company seal and signature on this the day of 20 



    I



            Signature of the First Account Holder                      Signature of the Joint Account Holder




    Witnessed By :                                             Witnessed By :

    Signature :                                                Signature :


    Name :                                                     Name :


    Address :                                                  Address :


04

